<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>@eason's notes</title>
    <description>Micro posts.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 01:55:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes.xml</link>
    <atom:link href="https://better.easoncao.com/notes.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-17</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Go to office is like doing social purpose and it may not perfectly optimze my working flow, ignored the meditation this time due to office rushs. But met people and had a conversation always is the nice part.&lt;br /&gt;
Three things gratituded: (1) Know a nice asian food restuarant near the office (2) Tried to do something great, and spread positive things and good feeling with people. e.g. shared protien kits (3) Had oppertunity to talk, exchange ideas, built connections, without any intention&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 01:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206170155</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206170155</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-15</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Feel calm and usual today, decided to have a run after thinking for a while. Go to office tomorrow.&lt;br /&gt;
Three things gratituded: (1) Correctly prioritize own work without concerning external pressure (2) Walked out and had 3.8 km run (3) Had oppertunity to coach and got positive feedback from other new hire engineer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:11:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206151111</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206151111</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-14</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Appreciated that I can have a bunch of time to do things I want, without interruption, and tried to slow down a little bit, did self-wellness. Also, the honey and lemon menthol sweets tasted great. &lt;br /&gt;
Three things gratituded: (1) Thanks deliveroo team reviewed and refunded my problematic orders. (2) no interruption can push project progress today. (3) thanks rider delivered my foods, had a great oppertunity to be kind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 22:35:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206141035</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206141035</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-13</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Took a few minutes to do meditation, probably start to feel peaceful and not too be anxious, remember to take deep breath. New KR engineer onboard in Dublin, so grateful that I have these great oppertunity to meet different people from everywhere.&lt;br /&gt;
Grateful things: (1) Got many medical suggestions from Tim, codinex for dry coughs relief from Edward. Really appreciate to their cares. (2) Walked out for gym after hesitating for a couple of hours. (3) Contributed my knowledge at work and helped primary issue.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 22:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206131054</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206131054</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-12</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I was depressed due to two orders did not be delivered due to service bug, the customer service did not help me and I need to write email to claim. 3rd order with UberEats also got issue. Whatever, at least I am still feel grateful because I have food to eat. Sometimes just try to think it in another way, things will get better. I knew getting mad doesn’t help, so still appreciate to anyone who reviewed my orders and tried to help me figure out.&lt;br /&gt;
Three things I felt thankful: (1) still have food to eat although delivery was missing (2) had a lazy day to slow down (3) learned new lession regarding preparing course from a good engineer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 22:32:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206121032</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206121032</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-11</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I went to gym and pick up the bar, the weight seems light, talk few words with gym people, hilarious!&lt;br /&gt;
Three things gratituded: (1) Got a full box of Tawian foods (2) had PM lession by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/standuploser&quot;&gt;Daniel Wu&lt;/a&gt; with NEX foundation (3) Walked to gym, no hesitate&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:35:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206110835</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206110835</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-10</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I was doing nothing. Sleep, meditate and review my own sansactions. I definitely need to sleep well, eat well and exercise well. &lt;a href=&quot;https://layaeap.ie/wellbeing/57&quot;&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Three gratitude things today: (1) sleep earlier (2) good customer service let my deliveroo order rescheduled (3) the rainy day cleaned my window&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 19:20:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206100720</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206100720</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2022-06-10</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting to do journaling because I noticed my mental health issue needs to find a way out. Since last year, I started to aware that I was in the path to burnout, and it’s time to start write down something as it might be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the first time I got cold in Ireland and it is totally breaking my working belief, start to thinking I should treat myself well, because it has been a while I never really take a reset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can feel depression, lose motivation and not in interested to thing what I love sometimes. But I figured out try to do things slow looks like helps, try to do less, focus on one thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things to focus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;have good sleep (sleep before 11:00 PM)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;use balance app and do meditation 10-15 minutes everyday&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three gratitude things today: (1) start writing daily note (2) had time to enjoy &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;It's Kind of a Funny Story&lt;/code&gt; (3) have warm, sunny and good weather&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.helpguide.org/articles/stress/burnout-prevention-and-recovery.htm&quot;&gt;Burnout Prevention and Treatment, HelpGuide.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
—&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.verywellmind.com/what-to-do-when-you-have-no-motivation-4796954&quot;&gt;What to Do When You Have No Motivation, verywellmind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206101250</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://better.easoncao.com/notes#t202206101250</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
